Okay,
good morning everyone and we're joining
Good morning everybody. We are just uh
we have quite a few people who are
joining us and so our lobby is right now
letting everybody in. So please bear
with us for a few moments as we have uh
everybody joining.
And again please bear with us. We do
have a couple of people who are still
joining the meeting. Uh uh as we do have
quite a few people who are interested in
this board meeting. So uh we already are
over 85 attendees. Um and so please give
us just a moment. We want to make sure
we can get everybody into the meeting.
Okay, good morning everyone. Uh my name
is Dr. Dominic Zerlo and I prefer to be
addressed as Dominic. Um and I'd like to
welcome everybody to our first uh
medical psilocybin advisory board
meeting. Uh it seems as though the
people joining has slowed down a little
bit. So we'll go ahead and get started.
Um and uh hopefully [clears throat] that
we'll be able to get through the agenda
that we have and be able to get to
public comment and [snorts] actually be
able to answer questions that people may
may have uh with regard to the board
members themselves. Now, just to let
everybody know, when we do get to the
public comment, we will be um uh we will
be taking comment, but we will not have
time to answer questions during this
meeting. We will be recording those
questions because we want to make sure
that everybody will have time to speak.
And so, we'll record those questions and
then we'll publish an FAQ here in about
a week, give or take a little bit, so
that we can make sure we have answers
for everyone. Um, in the meantime, um, I
would like to introduce Senator, uh,
Jeffrey Steinborn, who is here joining
us today and was one of the primary
sponsors of Senate Bill 219. And so, uh,
the floor is yours, Senator.
>> All right. Good morning, everybody. I
hope folks can hear me. Okay.
It is it is a real honor and it's very
humbling to be with you today and and to
get to help to kick things off. Um,
thanks everybody who who were able to
join this morning. I am State Senator
Jeff Steinborn. I was honored to be the
lead sponsor of a bipartisan group of
sponsors in the Senate, New Mexico
Senate and House who introduced the
Medical Psilocybin Act. And uh I just
want to say to state the obvious or
maybe not this is really a historic day
not just for the state but really even
for the whole country and the whole
world as we are experiencing a um a new
renaissance I'll say because it's not
the first one but a new renaissance of
psychedelic medicine and as we know New
Mexico becomes only the third state in
the country to create a formal public
program for the use of of this medicine
and and recognizing the humility of of
this moment, I I want to thank all of
the all of the advocates and
practitioners who have been doing this
work and advocating for this medicine
for a very long time um in New Mexico
and nationally. I want to thank those
policy leaders who have been advocating
for this medicine for a very long time,
decades. And I want to thank of course
and honor indigenous communities who
have been using this sacred plant
medicine for thousands of years whose um
knowledge
um and wisdom we are certainly um
learning from and drawing from and
honoring as well. Um finally of course I
want to thank the department of health
for um standing up this program really
in good time and not just by government
standards by anyone's standards. um they
are really passionate about this mission
and that's obvious and I think we can
all feel really good about that. Um and
and lastly want to congratulate all the
new advisory board members that that
have been appointed to this new
endeavor. Congratulations to you and
thank you for taking this work on. Um I
want everyone to know that the
legislature fully supports this um
stands behind you in this work to make
this a successful program. and uh just
kind of [clears throat] give you a
little note of encouragement as you move
forward recognizing that we're only the
third state to do this. By definition,
we're pioneers and we're going to um
we're going to learn a lot, but but I
also want to challenge you to not be
afraid to to try new things, to
innovate, to make things better than
maybe they've been in other states. in
some cases maybe they've gone down a
road that hasn't been as fruitful that
we need to deviate from. So I think
we're going to be inclined to learn from
them but also let's let's build the very
best thing we can build here and um
never be afraid to use your voice to to
to challenge that and to to to call for
that. And uh you know others of course
are are looking to New Mexico right now
to see how we do. And so this is this is
not just as New Mexicans counting on you
all to do good work and roll out a safe
but also um accessible program but also
how other states learn from that. So um
I look forward to supporting your work
and I congratulate you and uh and I
really um just am honored to be here
with you all and thank you Dominic for
the opportunity to say a few words.
>> Thank you Senator. we really appreciate
you being here and uh none of us would
actually be here on this call without
the work of you and your other
colleagues in the New Mexico
legislature. Um and so we really
appreciate your being here especially in
this historic launching of the advisory
board.
>> Thank you.
Uh so just a few items from a
housekeeping standpoint so everybody is
aware because this is the first meeting
for the advisory board. Some of the
items on the agenda are to start looking
at uh the bylaws for the advisory board
and as well as the beginning of uh
discussion for electing a chair and a
vice chair for the advisory board. Um
however until that occurs I will act as
a moderator for this meeting. uh unless
there are any objections with regard to
from the board members.
Okay. Well, with that we'll proceed. Um
and again, uh what I really just wanted
to go ahead and do and for those who are
joining late, my name is Dominic Zerlo
and I am the director for the center for
medical cannabis and psilocybin. And uh
and just as a note, we are actually at
this point over 110 people on this
meeting at this point in time. So um
this is uh it's fantastic to see this
this many people participating and we're
going to try to do our best to be able
to hear all of those individuals who are
here for the public comment. Um but the
first thing that we really wanted to be
able to do is introduce our board
members, uh our newly appointed board
members. And for those who uh saw the
link that I posted in the chat just a
few moments ago, we do have the board
members with a brief bio for each of
them uh listed um on our website at this
point for the psilocybin advisory board.
And so if you go to that link that I
posted um and I'll post it again here in
just a moment. Um what you will see is
the very first link there says please
meet the medical psilocybin advis
advisory board members and uh if you
click on that you'll be able to actually
see their brief bios but with that in
mind I'll go ahead and I'll start if we
could have Brenda uh Burgard. Brenda if
you could go ahead and unmute yourself
and uh go ahead and uh introduce
yourself.
Hello everyone. Thank you for having me.
Um, I'm honored to be serving on the
board here. I am an LPCC
uh art therapist and licensed in
addiction. I also um been living in New
Mexico for gez about 48 years now and
love the culture here and I want to help
be able to serve here everyone and
listen to everyone what they have to say
and help to u form whatever we need to
in order to move forward with uh this
program with the medical program with
psilocybin. So thank you all for being
here and thank you for electing me to
the board. really appreciate it.
>> Thank you, Brenda. And Alana Dances, if
you'll unmute yourself and introduce
yourself.
>> Sure. Hi, I'm Alana Dances. Uh I am uh
for the rest of today the chief medical
officer of the Medicaid program and I
will be the acting Medicaid director
starting on Monday. Uh by Yeah. uh by a
um training I'm a nurse practitioner uh
specializing in geriatrics and uh still
practice a little bit seeing patients.
>> Thank you Alana and welcome. Uh next Ian
Dunn if you'll go ahead and unmute and
introduce yourself.
>> Hi everyone. Um thank you Senator
Steinborn for um you know creating this
institution so that we can all be here.
Uh, I want to thank the Department of
Health for appointing me. My name is Ian
Dunn. Uh, I am a nursing and psychology
student at the University of New Mexico.
I'm also a patient who has PTSD, a
qualifying condition under this program.
I hope to be able to advocate for my
fellow trauma experienced people and to
help bring them access to medications.
Currently, we don't have a good lot of
good treatments for psychiatric ailments
and I hope that this will be one that we
can provide.
>> Thank you, Ian. Uh, Desba and if you can
please unmute yourself and introduce
yourself.
My name is Desba. Um, I was born in
Santa Fe. I live here in Santa Fe. Um, I
have a uh, background in geology. So,
that's my science background from
Ammeris College in Massachusetts. Um, I
grew up in northern New Mexico um, and
around one of the highest overdoses for
um,
uh,
sorry, drug uses here in New Mexico. Um,
so I grew up around a lot of um, trauma
and didn't realize until much later when
I went away to college and had a hard
time coming back and being back in New
Mexico that how really much everything
in our generations and our culture um,
from genocide and and so forth had
really affected not only my upbringing,
my cultures upbringing being Navajo, but
especially also in northern New Mexico.
um walking to the Santoario, I was
always told there's needles. You know,
you [snorts] can't go to the playground
because there's needles
and just how much that that is something
that we need to live through to survive.
Um I'm also a licensed massage therapist
currently practicing. Um most currently
I am in the uh film industry as a
storyteller. People have al often asked
me how do all those three combine. Um,
the land tells stories, our people tell
stories, our bodies tell stories, and so
therefore, I feel like I'm a
storyteller. So, I'm learning to combine
all of these things. And it wasn't until
um I had my own um family break about 10
or so years ago that I was introduced to
the use of psilocybin and its beneficial
therapeutic uh qualities. Since then I
have progressed on to working in doing
meditations and how that has also helped
that it's not just about
um making that uh disconnection from the
medicine with our brains but it's also
about doing the work and I feel like
this is an opportunity for New Mexico to
do the work intentionally to move the
rest of the country and the world
forward and what better place to do that
than here in our own cultural sacred
area. So thank you. I really appreciate
the opportunity.
Thank you, Despa, and welcome.
Uh, Dan Jennings, if you would unmute
and introduce yourself.
>> Hi, everybody. I'm Dan Jennings. I, uh,
am living in Hagermanerman. I've lived
here all my whole life. We're about 900
people. We are outside of Roswell, New
Mexico. I serve as a town counselor here
in Hagermanerman and I run a nonprofit
Haggerman Forward and work with 100%
Chavis initiative and we're focused on
10 vital service sectors including
mental health. Uh and through that work,
I wrote the opioid solutions grant fund
uh plan for the county and got that
submitted. And so now we're working on
utilizing the opioid settlement funds to
actually work a lot in mental health.
And uh a lot of my background comes from
spending 20 years working for Department
of Corrections here in New Mexico,
recidivism reduction bureau at the Rosal
Correctional Center. And I'm just I I
have to say uh I'm honored and humbled
to be part of this group. I have to say
I have a little bit of imposter syndrome
right now because this is a fantastic
group of people and I'm just really
excited to be part of this commission
and hope I can make positive
contributions and represent New Mexicans
and in this quest to improve the lives
of so many. And thank you.
>> Thank you, Dan, and welcome. Uh, and
Larry Leman, if you'll unmute and
introduce yourself.
>> Great to be here. Thank you so much,
Senator Steinborn, for the work of
yourself and your colleagues and Dom and
DO. Um, I'm a physician. I'm a family
and addiction medicine physician. Have
lived in New Mexico for 35 years. Um,
including seven years working in the
Zouri and Navajo reservations. Um I
involved now um fairly deeply in doing
psychedelic research at the university.
We're focusing on psilocybin and MDMA. I
came to this from um my experience of
dealing with trauma um working with as
the Magro medical director dealing with
trauma and pregnancy and looking for
ways that we could work on trauma and
addiction. So that's my passion. And um
I'm very interested in in uh supporting
us in developing a program that has a
strong community basis that has
equitable um um access as well as
safety. So delighted to be here with
everybody. Thank you.
>> Thank you, Larry, and welcome.
>> And Chris Piscus, if you can unmute and
introduce yourself.
>> Good morning, everybody. My name is
Chris Piscus. I'm a former staff
sergeant in the Marines and I'm an
expert in substance use disorder,
depression, and PTSD through lived
experience.
I was born in Sedro, New Mexico, and I
reside here in Albuquerque.
Currently,
I'm working on becoming a facilitator in
Colorado and just forming a deep
connection with the medicine. and uh I'm
an aspiring herbalist and a community
advocate and I'm just super grateful to
to be here among all of you and uh
really looking forward to getting to
work on this and helping a lot of
people.
Thank you Chris and welcome. So those
are our seven appointed board members at
this point in time. Um and in order so
that everybody uh on the meeting is uh
aware of our team that we have here at
the department of health, we'll go ahead
and do some very brief introductions. Um
so what I would ask is for my team
members just to introduce yourselves,
what your position is um and then we'll
go ahead and move forward. I do have two
people on our team that I will ask to
say a little bit more towards the end.
But in the meantime, um, if you will go
ahead and introduce yourself. Um, and
we'll start with Brenda.
>> Good morning everyone. Welcome. Happy to
be here. My name is Brenda Martinez. I'm
the deputy director with the Center for
Psilocybin and um, cannabis. Thank you.
>> Thank you, Brenda Rosalie.
>> Hi. Hey, good morning everyone. My name
is Rosalie Nava. I am the health program
manager for the health education team.
Happy to be here. Excited to be a part
of this.
>> Thank you, Rosalie. Raymond.
>> Good morning everybody. My name is
Raymond Gyos. I'm the uh systems and
data analyst for medical uh cannabis and
psilocybin.
>> Thank you, Raymond.
Uh, Rosanna Archeletta.
>> Hi everyone. Good morning. My name is
Rosanna Archeletta and I am the uh staff
manager here for the center for medical
cannabis and silicon. Welcome
>> Kathy.
>> Morning everyone. My name is Kathy Jerry
and I'm an information technology uh
project manager and I support the center
for medical cannabis and psilocybin.
Welcome.
Katie.
>> Good morning everybody. My name is Katie
Fry and I'm a health educator with the
program and delighted to be here.
Johnny,
and just so everyone is aware, Johnny
has actually been helping us as we've
had people had requests to get into the
meeting. Uh it looks like he may be
helping someone at the moment. So Johnny
is actually our management analyst for
the center and is helping us with uh and
Kathy with setting up the meetings and
logistics for the program.
Uh and then uh the two people I'm going
to ask to speak a little bit more is uh
Rob Truckner. Rob, if you can introduce
yourself a little bit.
Morning everybody. I am thrilled to be
here. It's starting now, isn't it? It's
exciting. I am the medical director for
psilocybin and for cannabis. I my
interests run from spore to the post in
integrative sessions. So I have to say I
look forward to working with all of you
getting your insights and your
perspectives so we can make one of the
most effective yet safe programs in the
nation. Thank you.
And the next person that I'd like to
introduce themselves, um, but before I
do that, I just want to let everybody
know that, uh, this is Jorge Gonzalez,
who is our new program manager for the
medical psilocybin program and is
actually our first hire specifically
dedicated for the program. So, Jorge, if
you'll introduce yourself.
>> Thank you, Dominic. Hello, everyone. Uh,
my name is Jorge Gonzalez. that it's
good to see all of you here. Thank you
for for being here. This is a as Senator
Steinborn said, this is a this moment is
huge for for New Mexicans and so thank
you all for being here and good to see
you and and welcome to our guests who
are also outside of New Mexico. Um my
name is Horge Gonzalez as I said
>> [snorts]
>> uh study here at the the College of
Santa Fe and the University of New
Mexico um in community and regional
planning and also my work in social
justice. uh my work around the state has
been around uh youth development,
community development, envir
experiential education, social emotional
learning. Uh but I feel like my
strengths are around networking and
bringing people together. Uh but as I
see here, there's a lot of people here
and so I look forward to that and I
really believe that uh truly us being
here as leaders is is really important
that we listen uh to our our local
keepers of wisdom. And so uh I feel that
moving forward in this moment that uh we
we be able to do that uh listen to the
keepers of wisdom and what our community
needs uh and then also that we have
access to medicine and we always keep
that at the forefront because we're
gathered here and making sure that
people's needs are met and and that
everyone has access to that and I think
that's really important uh things that
we keep in the forefront and and so so
thank you for being here and uh look
forward to to listening to you all and
and to meeting with you.
>> Thank you, Jorge. Um, and I just got to
note um that some people may not have
heard in the very beginning, although
you should have seen uh as you joined
into the meeting, this meeting is being
recorded and so just to ensure people do
know that they are being recorded. We
will be putting the recording up on our
website. Uh it does take a few days for
that to occur, but just in case people
do miss portions of this, we will put
the um the recording onto the website.
So I just want to make sure everybody
knows and understands that. So uh what
I'm going to do now is I'm going to just
share a little bit of information as far
as uh the program itself. Uh as you've
heard, we have hired our first dedicated
staff member in Jorge, our program
manager. We do have two additional
positions which uh the postings for
those just closed uh at the end of last
week and so we are just awaiting those
lists from our human resources and state
personnel office and then we'll be
starting to set up interviews for those
two positions. Those positions are an an
environmental scientist and a compliance
officer and they will be very helpful
and important in uh moving the program
forward especially with regard to
setting up the rules and regulations
along with the advisory board and
working with uh various providers and
potential cultivators as the program is
being set up. Now, within the statute
itself, um it it has been laid out that
we have until December 2027 to get the
program implemented. But as some of you
may have heard on some of the other
public meetings, because there has been
such large interest in this and a push
for us to try to be able to help people
um with psilocybin treatments earlier,
we have set a goal now to have the
program at least to be able to see the
initial patients by the end of December
of 2026. So it's a full year earlier.
And so we will go ahead and we will be
doing our best to try to move the
process forward. Now that does not mean
that all aspects of the program will be
ready by that December 2026. Um, and the
one thing that I do ask is starting up a
program at any time is a monumental task
and we want to be sure that we're
hearing information from people
throughout the state. And so we'll be
setting up various listening sessions
and additional board meetings uh as
things move forward, not just through
virtual settings, but also in person for
some of those. And so as we have more
information that will actually be posted
onto the program website. And so uh with
that in mind, if people are interested
in getting updates with regard to the
website, let me just share very quickly
how individuals can do that. Uh give me
just a moment and I'll share a couple of
slides.
Okay, I just want to check and make
sure. Can people see the PowerPoint
presentation?
I see some thumbs up and some head nods.
So, um, if individuals are interested in
getting updates on the program, we do
have a method where you can do so
electronically. And essentially, it's to
sign up for updates. There's just a few
steps. First step is you'll want to
visit www.nmhealth.org.
Once you do that, you'll see in the
upper right hand corner of the screen a
little uh indication, a little a link
saying sign up for e-news. And you'll
want to click on that link. Once you do,
it'll take you to a page that has a
little bit of sign up for e-news
information. And you'll just want to
complete that. Um and then
once you've done that then uh just click
on the medical psilocybin box. You can
also click on the other boxes that are
there if you're interested in other
information from the department of
health. But you'll just want to click on
that confirm that you are not a robot
and click on the sign up button that is
at the bottom there. And then you will
be signed up for our uh e updates. And
we do send out information through those
including uh information about meetings
uh updates about the program as we move
things forward and we do also include
job postings there in that uh through
that that process.
So with that in mind, so the other
update that I would like to provide with
regard to the program is um uh with the
program as we move things forward uh our
main staff and our main center staff are
located in Santa Fe, but the staff for
the psilocybin program we are located in
Albuquerque. And the main reason for
that is because it is a little more
central for the state to be able to get
out into the field to be able to meet
with community organizations with
various communities and with individuals
so that we can actually ensure that we
are uh getting the information from the
people that we need to get information
in order to set up a great collaborative
program.
So with that um the review Our next item
on the agenda is reviewing the purpose
of the advisory board. Now the purpose
of the advisory board is set out within
the statute and essentially it is to
review, recommend and create um medical
conditions for individuals who may
benefit from the medical use of
psilocybin
to accept and review those positions.
Recommend additional patient
qualifications.
recommend formulation and preparation
uh of dosage standards for psilocybin
and treatment standards.
also to be able to recommend and create
uh the the rules and regulations around
the medical psilocybin program and also
to assist the department in establishing
monitoring and determining the best ways
to evaluate what is occurring for
patients with producers, clinicians and
with other parties that are involved
with the program. And so those are the
main duties and responsibilities of the
board. And so what I'd actually like to
do at this time is uh to show this is a
draft of what we have actually created
um from a program standpoint just to
simply start um for the advisory board
itself for them to be able to see um
what potential bylaws would look like.
Now, for the members of the advisory
board, we have put this into your
SharePoint folder, which I know uh some
of you have been starting to access and
to look at. Um, but I'm going to go
ahead, pardon me, I'm going to go ahead
and share it on screen so you get an
idea. Now, we are not asking for you as
a board to vote on this at this time.
However, it is up to you to decide if if
you would like to do so, you may. Um,
however, what we usually re recommend is
that people review it and then make that
decision and make those votes at their
next meeting. So, uh, I just want to be
sure that everyone can see at this point
the document I'm showing that says med
medical psilocybin advisory board
procedures and bylaws. Seeing head nods
and thumbs up. Okay.
>> [snorts]
>> And just to go over very briefly what is
included in here, it lists down a little
bit of what the statute provides for
including what the membership of the
board entails.
Uh it includes then the board duties
which I just read a few moments ago and
then discusses what the membership and
voting eligibility which is essentially
that a board member is someone appointed
by the secretary
um and that a quorum uh shall consist of
attendance in the meeting by a majority
of members. So that [snorts] means that
in order to be able to vote on items um
then um you know you would need to have
a majority of people present to be able
to vote. It does also have that if
members miss three of the last
consecutive board meetings, they may be
asked to resign because one of the
things that uh in discussions with the
secretary and with others, we do want to
make sure that the board is going to be
an active and involved board. We do
understand that things happen sometimes
in individual's lives, but we do also
want to make sure that we're able to
move things forward.
Um and that a majority vote consists of
more than 50% of the voting members in
attendance at a meeting so long as there
is quorum.
That the meetings will be open to the
public. So that all meetings of the
board are going to be open. We will be
recording them. Um and again those
recordings will be posted to the program
website. Um and that uh the statute
requires that the board meet at least
twice a year. Uh my uh only comment on
that is that uh the board should
probably be meeting more often than that
and especially here in the beginning
stages I would recommend that you meet
much more often but that is up to you as
a board. Um all of the board meetings
will be announced 7 days in advance um
with the agenda posted one day prior.
That again is something that you as the
board members also have uh can decide if
you would like the board meetings posted
sooner uh and say for example at a
14-day or if you think a 3-day notice is
enough that is up to you and so what I
would recommend is that the board have
those discussions uh either here in a
few minutes or at the next meeting
before voting on it. Um and then again
with the agenda being posted, how soon
uh or how much in advance of a meeting
you would like that to be posted. And
then of course that the meetings will be
held at designated locations whether
that be in person or virtually but to be
done uh that'll be indicated within the
meeting announcement.
Um the next step is actually the
selection of a chair and vice chair is
that it'll be elected by a simple
majority of the board members during a
meeting.
um they're uh normally in that because
the secretary does actually appoint the
board members is uh with the approval of
the secretary of health. Um I do see
that one of the the board members has
gone in and done some editing. I think
that's fantastic to be able to go in. So
the other item was is that the chair
will conduct the meetings normally. Um
and that the chair may also be removed
by uh a either a simple majority or a
twothirds majority in the meeting of the
board which the quorum is present. And
again that's a decision for the board to
make on that. that a vice chair will be
elected by again a simple majority of
the board members uh and essentially
following the same process as the chair
including potential removal if needed
and that the change um of the bylaws is
established by a vote of twothirds
quorum of the board um and that
recommendations and actions that only
members of the board may propose or vote
on official actions of the board. Once
those the board has voted on the
recommendations, then the medical
psilocybin program staff will forward
that to the secretary for their
consideration. Um, and we had put in a
couple of different names for this next
section because different people and
different groups have different
preferences for names, whether it be
subcommittees, work groups, affinity
groups, however the board would like to
call them. Um, that will be up to the
board to determine, but that the board
may create these subcommittees and
designate chairs of them to explore
specific issues through a majority vote
of the board members and that the
committees should have specific tasks
and can be disbanded by a majority of
board members or when that specific task
is completed.
Um, and then that the committee report
to the board the completion of that
task. And then the usual and standard
conflict of interest essentially that
the board members not have conflicts of
interest and if they do have one they
will uh bring that on up and if
necessary if it is deemed to be a large
conflict of interest essentially to
notify the department of health and to
resign the position so that it can be
filled with someone without a conflict.
So, at this point, I'd like to bring
that on up and thank you to I'm not sure
which board member had gone in and done
some edits, but I'm very grateful to see
that. Oh, Ian, thank you. Very wonderful
to see that and see you already jumping
in since we only posted that to that
SharePoint website last night. So, uh I
do appreciate people already diving in,
but are there any um questions,
concerns, discussion from board members?
Uh Ian, go on ahead.
>> Um yeah, so I just kind of wanted to
explain I made a couple of changes. Um
one I took out that for our chair and
vice chair positions that we would need
approval of the secretary of health. I
figure it's an intra organizational
procedure to have a chair and a vice
chair and putting more work on the
secretary would just boggle things down.
So I struck that um given you know if
you look at our current federal congress
uh when you have just a simple majority
control the chair of the house nothing
gets done. So I scratched the simple
majority to a twothirds majority to
remove
um and I followed those same rules to
the vice chair and then just named um
the ad hoc subcommittees just committees
within the medical psilocybin board.
>> Thank you Ian.
other board members
al
>> yeah um just as far as the conflict of
interest um I think it needs to be a
little more robust I don't know if it's
like as far as what are considered you
know like financial how big financial
and I would also um
uh oh it does say affirm they have no
financial conflicts of interest I would
also request that when public there's
public comment that people are
disclosing any any conflicts as well.
>> Alana, just to be sure I'm understanding
you, you mean for uh the general public
speaking during public comment. We
usually do ask that individuals uh
disclose their organizations during that
time um and and who they're
representing. Um but uh this really
mostly affects and includes for the
board members themselves.
So but that's a great point and just so
you know we do usually do that um as far
as for public comments.
So what I would like to recommend to the
board is that um you all review this um
through the um the the rest of the uh
well the intervening period between now
and when the next meeting is set up and
that um if you do have edits uh that you
go on in go ahead and make those edits.
We are able to track changes. everything
in that document will be tracked so that
we'll be able to see uh if if we need to
revert back to for example a previous
version we can do so. So don't worry
about breaking it from that standpoint.
Um and then what I would recommend is
that uh unless anyone have an objection
you have that discussion during that
next meeting and vote on that. The one
exception that I would say uh on that is
if you all do decide to elect a chair
during this meeting, which is actually
the next item on the agenda. Um then
that uh the board just agree that that
would be a possibility to do. And if
not, I by the way, I'm happy to continue
moderating for this meeting and allowing
you all to elect a chair during the next
meeting. But I'll let you all decide
that.
Any thoughts, concerns, questions?
Personally
for me, um, we've just gone over the
bylaws as, uh, as a whole, read through
it with amendments, and we're allowed to
propose any questions. I would say let's
move to adoption, and then we can do the
vote on the chair.
>> Chris.
Yeah, I would like uh time to review the
um
review it further before we vote on it.
That would be my position on it.
>> Yeah, me too.
>> Okay,
let Oh, go ahead, Despa. Yeah, I I would
say if it's possible to motion to do to
table this until the next meeting to
vote on approval of it and um to then
move on to the next agenda item, which
would be to
uh find a chair and vice chair. That
would be my my motion.
>> I'll second Desbba.
>> I will clear that a motion.
>> Okay. So, so just so that you're all
clear because we actually don't have
bylaws yet. We don't have to do the
motioning at this point in time. Um, and
this meeting really is mostly as an
introduction and so that everybody can
start considering the different ideas.
But it sounds as though regardless there
is a majority towards uh reviewing it
over uh the next time period and
actually making decisions with regard to
the bylaws in the next meeting. So
unless there's any objections or if
individuals want to discuss it more. No.
Okay. So we'll go ahead and move forward
with regard to selection of uh chair or
vice chair. And um this is really again
this is up to you as individuals on the
board to make the decision on it. Um,
and you can do have the option to elect
somebody uh or for those two positions
today or again just like with the
bylaws, you can wait until next week
with regard to that. And if you do
decide to wait, I am happy to continue
moderating. Um, if you do decide to
elect somebody, um, then we'll, uh, be
moving forward with the other business
and setting a next date before we move
on to public comment. But so I'll open
it on up to the board members.
I would be okay with voting for chair
and vice chair as that doesn't really
set the rules too firmly. Um or we can
wait till the next. It depends on the
majority, but I think it would be fine
to do.
I
>> if that's the Oh, Dan,
>> I just saying I'd be willing to go along
with that as well to vote today.
>> Okay. Well, if that is the case, then
who uh would like to either nominate
themselves or one of the other board
members to be chair?
>> I'll nominate myself for the chair.
>> Ian,
others.
Well, if there are no objections, then
uh shall we proceed with Ian as the
chair for the board?
>> Yes.
>> Seeing seeing no objections, then how
about the vice chair
or would people like to think about
that?
Dan,
>> if uh I would be happy to be vice chair
in case would not be able to uh be at a
meeting or so if you would be okay with
that.
>> I'll second him.
>> Okay. And I'm seeing thumbs ups. Do we
have any objection of Dan being vice
chair?
>> Okay. At this point then we do have uh
Ian uh elected as chair and Dan as vice
chair. Um and so with that, our next
item of business is other business from
the board.
So
um I don't think the board has too much
um other business until we can um
establish those bylaws. That way we can
get you know committee started and that
kind of thing. So until um that I think
the only other business left on the
table would be um the next meeting date
unless anyone had some specific issues
that they would like to address. I just
feel the bylaws kind of have to have
precedence over new items.
>> Absolutely. We can definitely do that.
So, it does come down then to how often,
at least over the next month or two, the
board would like to meet.
>> So, we're all going into holiday season.
I'm sure um everyone on this board has
obligations to attend to. I would um say
let's do the third Friday in January,
which would be
my calendar doesn't want to load.
Uh 23rd of January and we can do it at
the same time if that works for
everyone.
I would be concerned about setting a
meeting during the legislative session.
>> Okay. Yeah. Um, we can definitely push
it out. So,
can someone remind me is it even
numbered years or oddnumbered years
where it's a 60-day?
>> It's a 30-day this year.
>> Okay. Yeah. Then we can push it out to
February
>> or or just the week before.
We could do it before that works too.
Um
>> like the 16th.
>> Okay. Of January.
>> Okay, that would work for me. Any
objections?
>> Okay, so January 16th at 9:00 a.m. works
for everyone.
>> No. Can I can I have a second? I feel
like we need to be meeting more
frequently than that. That's a month
away before we can even get started on
approving the
bylaws.
>> Can we not do that sooner?
>> I I would propose moving up a week
earlier. We have like, you know, we have
a really tight time frame to get the if
we're trying for 12 months.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I would say that Chris has a
really good point and there's a
possibility that we can meet more
frequently initially for a period of
time and then we can possibly move to um
maybe less frequently depending on our
the needs of the board.
>> Yeah, I would totally concur with that.
My um let me break down kind of my
understanding. So under the proposed
draft bylaws that we have, it would
allow for the creation of committees.
What that would do would say that the
whole board doesn't need to meet until a
committee has come together and said,
"Okay, well, here are the regulations
that we support for um production, let's
say, and then they could come and we
would have a big vote on it." So that
the whole board would be meeting a
little bit less. Um if you do want to
have more board meetings in the
beginning, we can totally do that. Um it
would just be
pretty soon, probably like a week from
today if you guys wanted to do that.
>> Well, I could do that.
>> I I could do that. Also, I would support
meeting in in a week or so and having
one of the first areas to look at what
the subcommittees could be. So then
people could start applying to be on
those committees and and be thinking
about that would move us along a little
quicker.
And I would like to recommend maybe I
know it's going to be difficult around
the holidays, but maybe bi-weekly
meetings after that. I I think we need
to be meeting much more frequently than
once a month.
>> Okay. Yeah. And as soon as our um you
know bylaws are finished, we can
definitely discuss the meeting amounts.
Um but I would support a twoe until we
had most of the um big issues that we
are assigned under SB219 settled
especially with you know that shortened
time frame right we want to get it done
by December 26th. So I would have no
objection to every two weeks of
meetings.
So, we're going to do a week from today
and then we can set the next um meeting
at that meeting.
>> So, that would be the 11th at 9:00.
December 11th,
>> December 12th.
>> Uh that's a Saturday.
December 12th.
>> Is it Friday?
>> Oh, I'm looking at 2026. I'm so far
ahead. Okay. [laughter]
>> Getting ahead of me now.
>> Okay. See, I'm already on top of it
here. All right. Great. That sounds
good.
>> All right. Perfect. Well, December 12th
at 9:00 a.m. will be the next meeting.
Is there any other um issues we want to
address? Any motions on the table?
Will we be meeting in person or online
or would it be a hybrid?
>> I'm going to defer to Dominic. Do you
have a preference on how we meet?
I I would just recommend due to winter
weather conditions that we conduct the
first uh few meetings virtually um just
because otherwise we may run into this
situation of people not being able to
travel or trying to travel and being uh
you know exposed to unsafe conditions.
So, I would just recommend uh doing the
next ones virtually uh the next couple
and what we'll do on the program side is
for next Friday at 9 a.m. we will get
that notice out as soon as possible
including with the links for it. And I
do apologize for the change in my view.
My computer decided to restart right uh
a minute ago and so I'm waiting for it
to come back on up. Um, but in the
meantime, as you can see, always have an
an another option available. And so I am
on my phone at the moment. My apologies
if people cannot hear me quite as well.
>> All right. And then um I believe the
last thing then we had to get to so
we'll be doing it online. Will, um, the
Department of Health be providing the
teams link and stuff how they kind of
did this time?
>> Yes, we will. We will get that out later
today and we'll get an announcement out
as well. Uh the announcement may take a
couple of days because we do have to run
it through our IT and they uh always
review items. So it may take a couple of
days for that announcement, but since we
are announcing it here, it will be a
public meeting. We will send it out
through those e updates that I mentioned
earlier. Um, and then once my computer
is back up, I'll also show that
information again on how people can sign
up for the e updates.
>> Will it be a two-hour meeting again?
>> Uh, that is up to you all.
>> And then Chris had a question.
Um,
>> just to finish, since I brought up, I'm
fine with the two-hour meeting. I just
wanted to have it clear so we put it on
our calendars.
Um,
>> how do others feel about Q hours?
>> Is there a good way to communicate with
each other in the interim that do we
just post on the SharePoint page or how
does that work?
Chris, what we will go ahead and do is
we can go ahead and connect each of you
uh through email so that uh if you want
to communicate, you can do so. The one
thing that I do want to caution everyone
on from a a transparency standpoint is
that um any communications among board
members are subject and are open to the
public. Um and so just to let you know
that would be the case. Um but uh we can
definitely set that on up so that you
all can communicate um through other
means as well.
All righty. And then is everyone ready
for public comment?
Okay. And Kathy, uh, if I may, Kathy, do
you have the list ready for the
individuals who had signed up?
>> I do. And so we'll start with those that
had requested to um provide public
comment when they registered for the
meeting. And then by using the um the
hand raising um button in the meeting,
you will be able to raise your hand. Um
if you did not register ahead of time
but wish to provide public comment
self
situated here with a timer. Um just as a
reminder um each person will have uh
three minutes and we will um
we'll
allow for um you to I guess speak again
if there's additional time remaining in
the meeting. Um but we'll go through
everyone um as a first pass first and
then if you would like to speak again
we'll kind of go through that process
again. Does that make sense?
Okay. So, let me get [sighs and gasps]
um
the first person
is sorry the list is so long I have to
uh expand it. Okay. So, the first person
um is Denali Wilson. Uh Denali um your
mic is activated if you would unmute.
You have three minutes.
>> Good morning um to the department and
members of the advisory board. My name
is Denali Wilson and I serve as the New
Mexico director of strategic support for
the healing advocacy fund which is a
nonprofit committed to expanding and
protecting safe, affordable, and
equitable access to psychedelic healing
for all who need it. I want to first
just express our gratitude. [sighs]
Thank you to all of the advisory members
for volunteering your time and your
expertise to help New Mexico build a
care system that meets the needs of
people struggling to find relief from
their suffering.
Our state is poised to lead the country
in the integration of psychedelic
therapy and our existing health care
system. And while it is important for
the program to move forward with
urgency, achieving the right balance of
safety, affordability, and equity will
require careful attention on
thoughtfulness. And so let's be sure
that any acceleration of the regulatory
timeline doesn't unintentionally
compromise patient safety, undermine
long-term sustainability, or limit
meaningful public engagement. But
whatever timeline the department
ultimately adopts, we will remain fully
engaged and offer recommendations on the
key parameters that will shape how the
care is delivered in New Mexico.
I want to briefly revisit a few
priorities that we've raised previously
during the department's listening
session over the summer. First is is
safety. We support balanced patient
safety guard rails. Um tiered and
tailored licensing and training
requirements so that care team members
receive the training unique uh and
appropriate for their role. A clear code
of ethics and strong systems for
measuring outcomes both in terms of
reporting adverse events and
comprehensively capturing the overall
program impact so that we can protect
patients and have what we need to
continually improve. Uh we also want to
see affordability and equity prioritize.
We want to urge the full funding of the
program's equity fund and are ready to
support the department's upcoming budget
request in the legislative session uh to
move in this direction with an earlier
timeline being discussed that pulls
services in as early as next year. The
equity fund must be prioritized in 2026
so that patients can access services
that we're building together. Uh, also
in affordability, we really encourage
regulations that keep care affordable.
Things like allowing
>> 30 seconds remaining,
>> group care models, adopting a broad
definition of clinician within the
rules, authorizing diverse care settings
and care teams, including peer support
workers and traditional healers, and
ultimately working to ensure that the
cost of this care can as much as
possible be covered by Medicaid and
private payers, private um, health
insurance. Thank you so much for your
time and your leadership. And that's all
I have.
>> Thank you.
>> Next we go to Scott Kennan.
Scott, your line has been um activated.
please unmute. You have three minutes.
>> Yeah, thank you. Um,
well, I'll just say I'm originally from
Tennessee, came over here to New Mexico
and I love it.
I left there because I didn't agree with
a lot of things that were going on. Um,
I am currently on the maximum dose of
two different anti-depressants,
but I still have a lot of haunting,
terrible thoughts due to PTSD
and depression.
I'm one of those people that you hear
about. I've had a terrible life from day
one. Actually, even before I was born, I
was exposed to drugs and trauma.
It still affects me greatly. I almost
drank myself to death for 20 years. I
got head injuries and all that kind of
stuff while I was doing that. Stop
drinking eight years ago, but I still
have the effects of the depression and
the PTSD.
Think my brain is damaged. This sounds
like something that really could help
me. I don't know. I'm always looking for
some kind of magic pill to take it away.
And these aren't magic pills. They're
magic mushrooms. But I I know there's no
it's not really magic, but I I'm also
interested if the um I know you don't
have a time to answer any questions, but
I uh I would like to know about how
psilocybin would be administered.
Um would it be a pill or a patch? Uh
I've heard that the mushrooms actually
taste terrible if you try to eat them.
That's why I'm asking. I would go
through that anyway. But um yeah, I'm
[snorts] just curious about that. And
also um I'm curious about how the
process would work. I have a therapist
here in Silver City whom uh I trust sort
of. I don't trust much of anybody, but
with her over the past seven years, I've
learned to trust her a little bit. um I
don't know if I could go to another city
somewhere and meet somebody that I've
never met before and trust them to guide
me through uh the process with the
psilocybin. So uh those are just things
I'm curious about and I thought I'd tell
you a little bit of my story and how I'm
very much looking forward to uh
psilocybin treatment if it actually does
come into place. So thank you.
>> Thank you.
Okay, next we have Brett Phelps.
Your mic has been activated. Please
unmute yourself. You have three minutes.
>> Uh Kathy Brett actually posted in the
chat that he was not going to provide
public comment at this time.
>> Okay. Thank you.
Okay. Uh, we'll go to next was
Greg Evans.
>> Greg, your mic has been activated.
Please unmute yourself. You have three
minutes.
>> Thank you uh for allowing me to speak.
My name is Gregory Evans. Uh, is my mic
working?
>> Yes, we hear you.
>> Cool. Thank you.
Um
yes, I am [clears throat]
interested in contributing in any way
that I can um to the development of this
program um whether it be through uh
committee or uh working directly for the
department of health. I have a
application in for the senior compliance
officer
position that is available and I'm look
forward to being able to talk with you
guys more u directly about that uh in
the future. Currently I work in uh
compliance and grant management at the
department of public safety and I feel
that my personal interest in um
making sure that we
move into a system where compliance
tracking for growth testing and
analytics
um merges well with the system of
physicians and caregivers.
So that dosage and understanding
questions like the previous commenter
was asking can be communicated
in an accessible manner to the public. I
feel that finding a way to reach the
finding a way to reach the
demographics that would not normally
know that they can benefit from this
medicine is essential. And I'll just
kind of like leave it there for for
today. Um, and also congratulations. I
am so proud that so many of you have
been able to show up for this and I am
really excited about the choices that
we've made for the board members here
today. Thank you.
>> Thank you.
>> Okay, next we'll go to uh Lida Fati.
Your mic has been activated. Please
unmute yourself. you have three minutes.
>> Good morning everybody. Thank you so
much for having me today and um thank
you for your presence and the beautiful
work you're doing for our community. U
congratulations to the advisory board
members and our state really as a
pioneer. Um my comment is um you know
kind of goes off of what Denali uh
mentioned about safety of our community
which then really begets that we need a
lot of education for those who will be
utilizing the SDS medicine um for
extensive therapeutic benefits
um and to learn from other states such
as Colorado and Oregon for the
unfortunate complexities ities that they
have created for facilitators and care
delivery to occur and um to make it less
complicated. You know, I'm in the world
of medicine. I'm a physician, hospice
physician and worked at UNM for a decade
as a hospital hospitalist academic
hospitalist and though enjoyed it
learned a lot but the complexities that
we have in the medical industry
um really creates so many complex
obstacles
for proper care delivery to patients. If
I want to help a patient with chronic
pain, it is nearly impossible to do so.
and it brings them to tears, it breaks
my heart. Um, and so for us to really be
aware of that when we are making these
rules and regs moving forward so that
those who really need help are able to
get it where they need to get it even
locationwise.
those with disabilities, those at the
end of life who can't leave home, they
should be able to get these medicines at
home. Um, so I I think we have an
incredible opportunity right now um as
leaders and pioneers. This is uncharted
territory in some ways, uncharted in
some other ways. and for us to be
creative in how we can really bring
these healing modalities into our
community with good common sense and
practicality as well. Thank you so much
for having me.
Thank you.
Next we will go to
uh Aaliyah Douty.
Um,
your mic has been activated. Please
unmute. You have
three minutes.
Your mic should be activated.
Okay, we will move to the next one.
Okay. Um,
next, um, we'll call on Adele Getty.
Adele, your mic has been activated.
Please unmute. You have three minutes.
Uh [clears throat]
well, thank all of you um so much. I
actually said that I was not going to
make um any public comments, but um
thank you so much for all of you who are
participating in this and have
volunteered. And um uh I guess one of
the things that I I would say is uh as
lima foundation and you know we put on
the enchanted state um earlier in
September. One of the ideas that we've
had is to um be able to make a very
short educational film as a result of
that event um that could be, you know,
used um both online and taken into, you
know, rural parts of New Mexico as a
educational
um you know, opportunity for people who
may have no idea about what psilocybin
many people cannot even pronounce the
word psilocybin.
Um and for them to understand you know
the importance and the positive effect
that um you know these you know
medicines can have inside our
communities at large. So um we're in the
beginning stages of that. We did film it
with three different cameras and we
think that there's a real opportunity
there as an educational event. So, thank
you.
>> Thank you.
>> Okay, we'll come back to Aaliyah.
>> Aaliyah, your mic is activated. Please
unmute. You have three minutes.
Aaliyah.
>> Hello.
>> Hello. Can you hear me?
>> Yes.
>> Okay, finally. I couldn't get it to
unmute. Sorry about that. Um uh my name
is Aaliyah Jodi. I'm a licensed doctor
of oriental medicine and also a
biodnamic cranial psychotherapist.
And I'm starting to train in thematic
experiencing work. I've been doing a
fair amount of research on medical use
of psychedelics, especially psilocybin
and
um I
uh work with trauma healing with fiveman
acupuncture in the craniosacral therapy
and I really really want to be working
in this field of holistic medical use of
psilocybin and also interested in
helping bring forward in whatever way
possible um this program in New Mexico
for as many people as possible in a
really safe, supported way. Um, so I'm
really excited about this program and I
want to be able to use this in my
practice. Um, and so, you know, I don't
know what the what the regulations are
going to be on who can who can work with
us, [laughter]
but I just want to have input on that.
And um I also want to mention Paul
Stamuts who's a mic famous micologist
from Washington and he's done a lot of
med research on medical use of
psilocybin and so I encourage people on
the board to um look into you know check
into him and and look into the research
that he's
um participated in.
Could
you hear me? Okay.
>> Yes.
>> Okay, great. That's all I have to say.
Thank you.
>> Okay, thank you.
>> Okay, next uh we have Ash Shelton. Um I
see an Ash in the participants list. I'm
disabling or allowing the mic. Um please
unmute yourself. you have three minutes.
>> Uh, I actually wasn't going to make a
comment. Um, just kind of hear kind of
listening in to see what's going on and
how things are going. Um, but I am a
mushroom farmer, so I'm here just kind
of seeing how things are going to move
forward. um seeing how what I do would
be implemented or used or what
opportunities would be there for local
farmers and to let us be part of this.
And that's basically it right now.
>> Thank you. Thank you.
Okay. Um,
next on the list was Anna Vendrelli, but
I don't see her in the meeting. So,
we'll go to
the next person uh was Katherine Orno,
but let me check the chat. I think I saw
that she said she wasn't going to give
comment. Nope, that was a different
Katherine. Um,
go ahead to Katherine Waro. Your mic has
been activated. Please unmute yourself.
You have three minutes.
>> Can you hear me?
>> Yes.
>> Okay. Excellent. Sorry that took me a
second. All right. Um, so thank you to
all of you that are donating your time
and energy towards this remarkable
project and thank you for the
opportunity to speak today. My name is
Katherine Waro and I'm a licensed
professional counselor and psilocybin
assisted therapist in Los Cusus. As New
Mexico builds this program,
affordability must remain a central
focus. We've seen what happened to
Oregon and Colorado where training
requirements and licensing fees have
created insurmountable barriers. Some
practitioners faced costs of over
$10,000 which pushed entire communities
out of participation, especially rural
rural providers, culturally rooted
healers, and those serving marginalized
populations. If we're not careful, we
risk creating a program that only the
wealthy can enter and only the wealthy
can access. New Mexico has an
opportunity to do this differently. We
can build a system that is ethical,
accessible, and grounded in harm
reduction, not one that recreates the
same inequities we have seen in the rest
of healthcare. Affordability is also a
safety issue. When training is
inaccessible, the people most deeply
connected to their communities,
indigenous healers, traditional
practitioners, guranderas, counselors,
peer support workers, they are excluded.
These are providers who often have the
strongest relationships with the people
who need the medicine the most. I also
want to highlight another essential
component, the value of firhand
therapeutic understanding of psilocybin
assisted therapy. This medicine cannot
be fully understood from theoretical
understanding and policy alone. The
nuances of set and setting, emotional
pacing, trauma activation, somatic
response, and integration become clear
in a way that research articles can't
capture. If any board member or working
group participant has not yet had the
opportunity to experience psilocybin
assisted therapy within a safe guided
therapeutic context, I encourage
creating space for that. Whether through
established facilitators, training
organizations, or approved community
pathways. These experiences consistently
lead to more grounded, compassionate,
and effective regulation.
New Mexico has the chance to build a
model that is safe, affordable,
culturally respectful, and
communitydriven. One that recognizes the
wisdom already present in our state and
center our state.
>> 30 seconds remaining.
>> Harm reduction as the guiding principle.
I would also like to comment on
something a previous commenter
addressed. I do think it would be a
great offering if we ha could have a
program in which non-csychedelic
therapists can attend treatment with
their clients to ensure they receive a
full experience of care and trust.
And then finally, um I just want to
again thank everybody for all the time
that they've put into this. Um I think
it's really important the work that's
being done. Thank you for your time and
commitment to this process.
Thank you.
Okay. Um,
next
as a registered requesttor to provide
public comment on the list was Jen
Clemente. Um,
confirm.
>> Uh, Kathy Jen,
>> she said that. Yeah, sorry at this time.
>> Okay. Yeah, sorry, but between the chat
and and the two different lists, it's
it's a lot. Um, okay. Let's see. Um, and
then next was
uh Gary Chavez, but I think I didn't see
them in the list.
>> Uh,
Gary is here. Yes.
>> Okay,
Gary, your mic has been activated.
Please unmute. You have three minutes.
>> Hi, thank you. Can you hear me? Okay,
there
>> we can. Thank you. Awesome.
Thank you all for having this uh group
come together. It's really uh been
inspiring to see this kind of take fold
um in the amount of time that it has. I
am coming more from
um a personal experience through this
process. I have been involved in the
medical cannabis program since 2011.
um just really looking at different
avenues for whether it was PTSD or
cancer or different elements that I
personally have gone through um through
these struggles. And so what's really
fascinating for me on this aspect is how
can we look at the newest, you know,
avenue that I really took about five
years ago was just dealing with my
alcoholism.
And so, you know, I wear many hats. And
so, for this specific uh, you know,
point that I'd like to get to is I tried
multiple different avenues. Um, you
know, psychedelics is the term we use.
You know, and the is the preferred term
that I can, you know, grasp towards and
share with folks. Um, that's, you know,
helped me through this pathway. Um, so
going through that, being five years
sober, um, recently getting off of
nicotine about nine months, uh, free
from that, a psilocybin has been my
biggest advocate through and through.
Um, I've both have experienced a macro
uh, dose as it's called, a hero dose, as
folks like to deem it, um, down to micro
and just trying different uh, pathways
for myself to heal. And so in any way
that I could be an advocate um for this
program, I'd love to see what I can do
to help the community um those that are
on the streets that are dealing with
mental illness up to, you know, we have
this um big push and balance from those
that have the the money. Um and so
it is important that there's no
distinguishability for me on a mental
state. We all struggle with it whether
you have money or don't have money. I
think that um you know what people have
touched on about this is it needs to be
accessible and that's my big push that
I'd love to see because I've been gifted
this uh these fruits if you would the
magic mushrooms um for free. I've, you
know, allocated them um through the
>> 30 seconds remaining.
>> And so in any way possible that I could
help advocate and push forth in a way
that people can have access to this
medicine, I'd like to just uh do my part
and I really hope that the the committee
here, the board, I appreciate your time
that that could happen. So thank you.